

CONTACT

- Bogura, Bangladesh
- +8801726389558
- <u>abidshahriar7@gmail.com</u>
- https://github.com/abid-shahriar
- https://linkedin.com/in/abidshahriar
- https://abidshahriar.me

SKILLS

- HTML | CSS | SCSS
- JavaScript | TypeScript
- ReactJS | NextJS
- Redux | ContextApi
- NodeJS | Express
- Mongoose | MongoDB
- Postgres | Prisma | Knex
- Git | Github
- DigitalOcean App platform | AWS S3

LANGUAGES

- Bengali (Native)
- English (Professional working proficiency)
- Hindi (Limited working proficiency)

HOBBIES

- Coding
- Travelling
- Cooking
- Gaming

ABID SHAHRIAR

Full Stack Web Developer

ABOUT ME

Creative full stack JavaScript Developer with 3+ years of experience and have a passion for building responsive, interactive and secure web applications. I have a strong background in web development and have worked on a wide range of projects. I like learning new technologies and always try to keep myself updated with the latest trends.

EDUCATION

Bogura Zilla School, Bogura

Secondary School Certificate(SSC) in Science Feb 2008 - Feb 2016

Govt. Azizul Haque College, Bogura

Higher Secondary Certificate(HSC) in Science

Feb 2016 - Feb 2018

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer

Valkyrie IT LTD | https://www.valkyrie-it.com/deck

Nov 2021 - Present

As a full stack dev., my responsibilities are creating secure and scalable backend and frontend, doing research on new technologies, testing UI and API to make sure everything is working as it should be.

Frontend Developer

Wikiance | https://wikiance.com

Nov 2020 - Sep 2021

I was the lead developer on their flagship project called Techiio. My responsibilities were implementing api by coordinating with backend developers, adding new features, testing, scaling up, bug fixing, training interns etc. Learned a lot about teamwork, communication, best practices, and how to work in a fast-paced environment from here.

Freelancer

Feb 2019 - Oct 2020

In my early days, I did freelancing with some local clients. I used to make school/restaurant and small e-commerce websites for them. After that I started freelancing with some remote clients. Gained a bunch of new skills doing these.